Deadly Inn is a thriller, tv movie film directed by John Murlowski.
A single mother restores a Victorian home and opens a bed-and-breakfast, but
the arrival of a guest with a hidden agenda shatters the peace.
Robyn Flynn, played by Angie Patterson.
Iris / Beth, played by Aria Pullman.
Drew, played by Chad Michael Collins.
Ava, played by Kate Mina Lin.
Professor Marcus, played by Gildart Jackson.
Sheriff, played by Randy Crowder.
Jill Suzanne Wagner (born January 13, 1979) is an
American actress and television personality.
She was the on-field host for the ABC game show Wipeout from 2008 to 2011 and again
from 2013 to 2014, briefly leaving during the fifth season in 2012.
Since then, Wagner has starred in several made-for-television films for the
Hallmark Channel, Hallmark Movies & Mysteries, and Great American Family.
She stars as Bobby in the Paramount+ spy series Special Ops: Lioness (2023).
The tone is intense.